And if all those dreams land
Oh my
That's just the way
I
You are all i want
So what am i going to do
And if you don't need to put the water
Keep in mind
I'm just a whisper of
Somehow slip right through you in the
We got eyes
But that's the
You're all i've got
So
What am i to do
And if you should care for me
That can do the will and
I can give me a memory
I'll give
I'm gonna get you and sailors go work it out
And they see you did
When we middle
I'll give me
I'm a free man
Give me
I love my home
I give up my you
Thank you so much apples saving for the wrapper
Um h
I'm getting out of the
I'm a walking the streets of today
You but yeah
I'm going away
I'm a walking
I'm here on my own
You say your life is only just begun over and over in the days of young
You always tell me that until you leave
Come on
Wake up for your illness
You say it's better enough for you to get cause
There will always be a story
I want you to tell me what the answers i'm like come on
But you my fault
No
I need the one that i had
I'm just the one that i've had you
Me call us song in the in the middle middle middle middle
My song got a song in the in the middle
In the middle
In the
I'm a walking the streets of today
I'm walking
Yeah
I'm going my way
I'm walking
I'm here on my own
I'm a walking
Alone
You say your life has only just begun over and over
And the day so young
You always tell me before you leave
Come on
Wake up from your
You say it's better
Now
We get together
Cause there will always be a story where i want you to tell me
What the hell is the school
Oh boy
Come on what you waiting for
I wish this summer in this morning
Like the doo
Ha ha ha
Oh my god
Run they
The time
Oh my god
Go
Wanna make a so fun
I beg you to god
I beg you man
Let me find my baby